export const problems = [
  {
    question: '1 x 1',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 2',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 3',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 4',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 5',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 6',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 7',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 8',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 9',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 10',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 11',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '1 x 12',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 2',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 3',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 4',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 5',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 6',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 7',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 8',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 9',
    answer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 10',
    answer: 20,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 11',
    answer: 22,
  },
  {
    question: '2 x 12',
    answer: 24,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 3',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 4',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 5',
    answer: 15,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 6',
    answer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 7',
    answer: 21,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 8',
    answer: 24,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 9',
    answer: 27,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 10',
    answer: 30,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 11',
    answer: 33,
  },
  {
    question: '3 x 12',
    answer: 36,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 4',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 5',
    answer: 20,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 6',
    answer: 24,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 7',
    answer: 28,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 8',
    answer: 32,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 9',
    answer: 36,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 10',
    answer: 40,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 11',
    answer: 44,
  },
  {
    question: '4 x 12',
    answer: 48,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 5',
    answer: 25,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 6',
    answer: 30,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 7',
    answer: 35,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 8',
    answer: 40,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 9',
    answer: 45,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 10',
    answer: 50,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 11',
    answer: 55,
  },
  {
    question: '5 x 12',
    answer: 60,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 6',
    answer: 36,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 7',
    answer: 42,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 8',
    answer: 48,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 9',
    answer: 54,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 10',
    answer: 60,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 11',
    answer: 66,
  },
  {
    question: '6 x 12',
    answer: 72,
  },
  {
    question: '7 x 7',
    answer: 49,
  },
  {
    question: '7 x 8',
    answer: 56,
  },
  {
    question: '7 x 9',
    answer: 63,
  },
  {
    question: '7 x 10',
    answer: 70,
  },
  {
    question: '7 x 11',
    answer: 77,
  },
  {
    question: '7 x 12',
    answer: 84,
  },
  {
    question: '8 x 8',
    answer: 64,
  },
  {
    question: '8 x 9',
    answer: 72,
  },
  {
    question: '8 x 10',
    answer: 80,
  },
  {
    question: '8 x 11',
    answer: 88,
  },
  {
    question: '8 x 12',
    answer: 96,
  },
  {
    question: '9 x 9',
    answer: 81,
  },
  {
    question: '9 x 10',
    answer: 90,
  },
  {
    question: '9 x 11',
    answer: 99,
  },
  {
    question: '9 x 12',
    answer: 108,
  },
  {
    question: '10 x 10',
    answer: 100,
  },
  {
    question: '10 x 11',
    answer: 110,
  },
  {
    question: '10 x 12',
    answer: 120,
  },
  {
    question: '11 x 11',
    answer: 121,
  },
  {
    question: '11 x 12',
    answer: 132,
  },
  {
    question: '12 x 12',
    answer: 144,
  },
  {
    question: '1 / 1',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '2 / 1',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '2 / 2',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '3 / 1',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '3 / 3',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '4 / 1',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '4 / 2',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '4 / 4',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '5 / 1',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '5 / 5',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '6 / 1',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '6 / 2',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '6 / 3',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '6 / 6',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '7 / 1',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '7 / 7',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '8 / 1',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '8 / 2',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '8 / 4',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '8 / 8',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '9 / 1',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '9 / 3',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '9 / 9',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '10 / 1',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '10 / 2',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '10 / 5',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '10 / 10',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '11 / 1',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '11 / 11',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '12 / 1',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '12 / 2',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '12 / 3',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '12 / 4',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '12 / 6',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '14 / 2',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '14 / 7',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '15 / 3',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '15 / 5',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '16 / 2',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '16 / 4',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '16 / 8',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '20 / 2',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '20 / 4',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '20 / 5',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '20 / 10',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '21 / 3',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '21 / 7',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '22 / 2',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '22 / 11',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '24 / 2',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '24 / 3',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '24 / 4',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '24 / 6',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '24 / 8',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '24 / 12',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '25 / 5',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '27 / 3',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '27 / 9',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '30 / 3',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '30 / 5',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '30 / 6',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '30 / 10',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '32 / 4',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '32 / 8',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '33 / 3',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '33 / 11',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '35 / 5',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '35 / 7',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '36 / 3',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '36 / 6',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '36 / 12',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '40 / 4',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '40 / 5',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '40 / 8',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '40 / 10',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '42 / 6',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '42 / 7',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '44 / 4',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '44 / 11',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '45 / 5',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '45 / 9',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '48 / 4',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '48 / 12',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '49 / 7',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '50 / 5',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '50 / 10',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '54 / 6',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '54 / 9',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '55 / 5',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '55 / 11',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '56 / 7',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '56 / 8',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '60 / 5',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '60 / 6',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '60 / 10',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '60 / 12',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '63 / 7',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '63 / 9',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '64 / 8',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '66 / 6',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '66 / 11',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '70 / 7',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '70 / 10',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '72 / 6',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '72 / 12',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '77 / 7',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '77 / 11',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '80 / 8',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '80 / 10',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '81 / 9',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '84 / 7',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '84 / 12',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '88 / 8',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '88 / 11',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '90 / 9',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '90 / 10',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '96 / 8',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '96 / 12',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '99 / 9',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '99 / 11',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '100 / 10',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '110 / 10',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '110 / 11',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '120 / 10',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '120 / 12',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '121 / 11',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '132 / 11',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '132 / 12',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '144 / 12',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 1',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 2',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 3',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 4',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 5',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 6',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 7',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 8',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 9',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 10',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 11',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 12',
    answer: 13,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 2',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 3',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 4',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 5',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 6',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 7',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 8',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 9',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 10',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 11',
    answer: 13,
  },
  {
    question: '2 + 12',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 3',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 4',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 5',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 6',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 7',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 8',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 9',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 10',
    answer: 13,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 11',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '3 + 12',
    answer: 15,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 4',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 5',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 6',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 7',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 8',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 9',
    answer: 13,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 10',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 11',
    answer: 15,
  },
  {
    question: '4 + 12',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 5',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 6',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 7',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 8',
    answer: 13,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 9',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 10',
    answer: 15,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 11',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '5 + 12',
    answer: 17,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 6',
    answer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 7',
    answer: 13,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 8',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 9',
    answer: 15,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 10',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 11',
    answer: 17,
  },
  {
    question: '6 + 12',
    answer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: '7 + 7',
    answer: 14,
  },
  {
    question: '7 + 8',
    answer: 15,
  },
  {
    question: '7 + 9',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '7 + 10',
    answer: 17,
  },
  {
    question: '7 + 11',
    answer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: '7 + 12',
    answer: 19,
  },
  {
    question: '8 + 8',
    answer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: '8 + 9',
    answer: 17,
  },
  {
    question: '8 + 10',
    answer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: '8 + 11',
    answer: 19,
  },
  {
    question: '8 + 12',
    answer: 20,
  },
  {
    question: '9 + 9',
    answer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: '9 + 10',
    answer: 19,
  },
  {
    question: '9 + 11',
    answer: 20,
  },
  {
    question: '9 + 12',
    answer: 21,
  },
  {
    question: '10 + 10',
    answer: 20,
  },
  {
    question: '10 + 11',
    answer: 21,
  },
  {
    question: '10 + 12',
    answer: 22,
  },
  {
    question: '11 + 11',
    answer: 22,
  },
  {
    question: '11 + 12',
    answer: 23,
  },
  {
    question: '12 + 12',
    answer: 24,
  },
  {
    question: '1 - 1',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '2 - 1',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '2 - 2',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '3 - 1',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '3 - 2',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '3 - 3',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '4 - 1',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '4 - 2',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '4 - 3',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '4 - 4',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '5 - 1',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '5 - 2',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '5 - 3',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '5 - 4',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '5 - 5',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '6 - 1',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '6 - 2',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '6 - 3',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '6 - 4',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '6 - 5',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '6 - 6',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 1',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 2',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 3',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 4',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 5',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 6',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '7 - 7',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 1',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 2',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 3',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 4',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 5',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 6',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 7',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '8 - 8',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 1',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 2',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 3',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 4',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 5',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 6',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 7',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 8',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 9',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 1',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 2',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 3',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 4',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 5',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 6',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 7',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 8',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 9',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 10',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 1',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 2',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 3',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 4',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 5',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 6',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 7',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 8',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 9',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 10',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '11 - 11',
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 1',
    answer: 11,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 2',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 3',
    answer: 9,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 4',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 5',
    answer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 6',
    answer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 7',
    answer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 8',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 9',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 10',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 11',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 12',
    answer: 0,
  },
];
